Guide to the Movement (Protest) Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Movement (Protest) collection
1946-1980
MS 617
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
36.5
(65 boxes)
An intentionally assembled collection of newspapers, pamphlets, leaflets, broadsides, and miscellanea relating to anti-war, socialist, student, and radical political movements in the United States, Africa, Europe, Asia, and Latin America, 1946-1980.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of various donors. Accession 2001-M-051 gift of David Dellinger, 2000.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
An intentionally assembled collection of newspapers, pamphlets, leaflets, broadsides, and miscellanea relating to anti-war, socialist, student, and radical political movements in the United States, Africa, Europe, Asia, and Latin America, 1946-1980.
The bulk of the West German student protest literature in this collection comes from left-wing groups, ranging from moderate socialist to Maoist, with many nuanced variations of political affiliation in between. The topics under discussion, while largely concerned with local university issues, also refer to international politics, local or national problems and ideological disputes with rival political groups. There is also a small amount of material from religious organizations, unions and ad hoc committees formed around particular issues. Single sheet leaflets make up the bulk of the German-language material although there are also scattered issues of newspapers, pamphlets and special documents.
Under the heading "Berlin," the reader will find literature issued by the Notgemeinschaft für eine freie Universität, an organization formed in 1969 to combat the effects of the left-wing student groups. Based in Berlin, this committee's primary interest is the Free University of Berlin, although its publications and reprints also cover topics dealing with the universities in general and problems in contemporary German education at all levels. Its publications are mostly in German, with occasional reports in English. One Notgemeinschaft publication in English offers an overview of recent university history in Berlin: The Situation of the Berlin Universities, 1969-1973, issued in 1973.
Arrangement
Arranged in two series and three additions: I. Underground and Radical Newspapers, 1946-1978; II. Pamphlets, Leaflets, and Broadsides, 1946-1979.
Politics and literature; Politics and war; Radicalism; Student movements; Students -- Political activity; Underground press publications; Africa -- Politics and government; Europe -- Politics and government; Europe; Germany; Latin America -- Politics and government; United States -- Politics and government; Broadsides (notices); Newspapers; Pamphlets; Yale University -- Students
- Underground and Radical Newspapers, 1946-1979; Series I
  Arrangement
  The newspapers are listed alphabetically by title.
  - About Face, 1972 April-May (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Volumes 2-3.
  - ACT (The RITA's Newsletter), 1970, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Volumes 1-2, plus miscellaneous RITA materials.
  - The Advocate, 1971 September-October (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Volumes 4:5-4:6.
  - African Agenda, 1973 September (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Volumes 2:9.
  - AIM (American Independent Movement Newsletter), 1969 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Volume 4:11.
  - Akwesasne Notes, 1970 Oct, 1972 Late Spring, 1974 Jun, 1976 early summer (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    Volumes 2:6, 4:3, 6:2, 8:2.
  - Alert: Women's Legislative Review, [1974?] (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Number 2.
  - Alert Communitarian. Newsletter, 1973 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Volume 2:3.
  - Alerta (Ecaudor), 1973 December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Al-Islam, 1973 Summer (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Volume 1:2.
  - Ally, 1968 February-Jun, 1968 August-1969 Dec, 1970 March-1971 May/Jun, 1974 January (Box 2, Folder 1-7)
    Volumes 1-5, 8-22, 24-35, 43.
  - Alternate Society, 1971 August-September (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Volumes 3-6.
  - Alternatives Journal, 1972 September 1-December 31 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Volumes 2:1-2:8.
  - Alternatives Newsletter, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Volumes 1:1, 2:2-2:3.
  - Alternatives Newsmagazine, 1971-1972 Summer (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Volumes [no volume number], 2-3.
  - American Avatar, 1968 October-December (Box 2, Folder 12-15)
    General note
    See also: The Avatar
  - American Exile in Canada, 1969 March 9-1970, 1971 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    Volumes 1:12-2:7, 2:9. Name changed to AMEX-Canada for volume 1:16 and then to AMEX: The American Expatriate in Canada.
  - American Report, 1973 February 12, 1974 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Volumes III:10, IV:18.
  - The Anarchist, 1966 October (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Volume 1:1.
  - Ann Arbor Sun, 1971 April 30-May 6 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Volume 1.
  - The Arctic Arsenal, 1971 May (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Asamblea Popular (Chile), 1972 May, August (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Volumes 409, 414.
  - The Avatar, 1967 June 9-22, July 7-October 27, November 10-1968 January 18, February 2-April 25 (Box 3, Folder 5-13)
    See also: American Avatar
    Volumes 1:1, 1:3-1:5, 6-10, 12-16, 18-23.
  - Aware, 1970 June (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Volume 2:1.
  - Baloney Moccasins, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bandera Roja (Chile), 1972 August (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Baumholder Gig Sheet, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Berkeley Barb, 1969 August 22-28, October 31-November 6, November 14-20. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Volumes 9:8, 9:17, 9:19.
  - Berkeley Tribe, 1971? August 14-20 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Volume 6:1.
  - Black Mask, 1967 May-Jun, October-November (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Volumes 6, 8.
  - Black Mesa Defense Fund
    See: Myths and Techno-Fantasies
  - Blacknews, 1971 March 28 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Volume 1:30.
  - Black Panther, 1970 March 28, April 11, April 18-May 2, May 19-June 6, August 1, August 8, October 31, December 14, 1971 February 27, May 1, May 15, June 12, September 18, October 16, October 30, December 25, 1972 January 15 (Box 4, Folder 8-13)
    Volumes 4:17-4:18, 4:20-4:22, 4:24-4:27, 5:4, 5:6, 5:18, 5:24, 6:5, 6:13-6:14, 6:16, 6:20, 7:4, 7:8, 7:10, 7:18, 7:21.
  - Boletin de Comite Central PS [Partido Socialista] (Chile), 1971 August-September (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Volumes 15-16.
  - The Bond, 1968 January 28-1971 September 25, 1971 November 26-1973 November 5, 1974 January 8, September-October (Box 5, Folder 2-9)
    Volumes 2:1-5:9, 5:11-7:5, Special #, 8:1, 8:4.
  - Boston Community News, 1969 May 22-June 22 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Volumes 1-2.
  - The Boston Free Press, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    See also: Broadside
    See also: The Free Press
    Incomplete copies of issues #1, 5.
  - Bread Box, 1971? October 20 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Volume 4.
  - The Broadside, 1966 May 11, 1967 March 1, March 15, April 26, May 24, August 16, September 13, September 27, 1967 October 25-1968 March 12, 1968 March 27-1969 July 29 (Box 6, Folder 1-14)
    See also: Boston Free Press See also: The Free Press
    Volumes 5:6, 61-6:2, 6:5, 6:7, 6:13, 6:15-6:16, 6:18-7:1, 7:3-8:11.
  - Brooklyn Bridge, 1971 March (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Bulletin, 1969 September 22, 1969 November 3-1970 January 19, 1970 March 16, 1971 October 25, 1976 January 13, February 6 (Box 7, Folder 2-4)
    See also: Racism and Black Power See also: Worker's League
    Volumes 6:2, 6:5-6:15, 6:23, 8:8, 12:4, 12:11.
  - Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars, 1972 Fall-December (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Volumes 4:3-4:4.
  - Burning River, 1970 May 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Volume 1:5.
  - Cahiers de Mai, 1968 January 15, July 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Camp News, 1972 April 15, August 15 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Volumes 4:3, 3:8 [?].
  - Cara a Cara (Chile), 1972 August 15 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Carta de Guatemala, 1965 Oct, 1966 January (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Volumes 3, 5.
  - Catholic Worker, 1973 October-November (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Volume XXXIX: 8.
  - Center for Cuban Studies Newsletter, 1975 July-December (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Volumes 2:3-2:5-6.
  - Challenge, 1970 Apr, October 5, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Volumes 7:1, 7:8, Extra (GE), GI Special.
  - Change (Washington Area Newsletter on Alternatives), 1972 May-August (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Volumes 1:3-1:4.
  - Chile Newsletter, 1975 September (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Volume II:4.
  - Chile Vencerá, 1975 Fall (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Volume 1:3.
  - Clear Creek, 1971 May (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Colonial Times, 1971 October (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Columbia Daily Spectator, 1968 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Volume LXII:103.
  - Combat: Perspectives for Struggle and Unity (Ethiopian Students Union in North America), 1974 April (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Volume 2, #3.
  - Conciencia Proletaria (Chile), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Volume 2.
  - The Coyote, 1971 Spring (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Daily Rag, 1972 Oct, 1973 February 223, May 4-18, June 15-August 24, September 7, November 2-9 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    Volumes 1:1, 1:9, 1:15, 1:18-1:24, 2:5.
  - Daily World, 1970 April 15, May 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Volumes 2:193, 2:205.
  - D.C. Gazette, 1970 July 13-September 20, 1971 March 29-April 25 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Volumes 1:19-1:21, 2:11-2:12.
  - Democratic German Report, 1972 December 13, 1973 Jan17-Jan31 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Volumes 21:22, 22:1-22:2.
  - Democratic Left. Newsletter., 1973 Apr, 1974 January (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Volumes 1:2, 2:1.
  - Demokratia, 1968 Dec, 1969 Apr, 1975 March (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Volumes 1:8, 1:12, 91.
  - Direct Action, 1972 March 20 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Volume 124.
  - The Dixon Line, 1969 December-1970 January (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Volumes 7:2-7:3.
  - Edcentric, 1971 May-June (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Volume 3:4.
  - L'Enragé, Undated, 1968 June 10-July 8 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Volumes 1-7.
  - EPF Newsletter, 1970 Summer (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Exile Report, 1971 March (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Eyewitness, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Volume 3:6.
  - Fateh, 1971 April 12 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Volume 3:2.
  - FE en la Revolucion Peronista, 1973 April 19 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Volume 2:14.
  - The Fifth Estate, 1967 August 15-31 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Volume 2:10.
  - FIN: Fuente de Información Norteamericana (Chile), 1972 August (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Forward, 1973 December (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Volume 19.
  - The Free Press, 1968 May-August (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
    See also: Boston Free Press See also: Broadside
    Issues 1-10.
  - Frente Brasileño de Informaciones (Brazil), 1971 December-1972 Jan, May-Jun, August (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Volumes 26/27, 31/32, 34.
  - FTA with Pride, 1971 June-Sep, October-Nov, 1972 October (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Volumes 1:2-1:5, 2:1-2:2, 3:4.
  - FTA with Pride (Tri-Cities Chapter), 1972 July-Oct, 1972 December-1973 January-May (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Volumes 1-3, 5-8.
  - Full Tilt, 197? July (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Volume 1:4.
  - Fusion, 1971 April 30 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Volume 55.
  - Gaceta de Junta, 1970 February (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - El Gallo, 1967 July 28 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Graffitti, 1968 May, 1969 Oct?, 1970 June-Jul, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Volumes 1:1, 2-5.
  - Grass Roots, 1972 October 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Volume 1:11.
  - El Grito del Norte, 1971 October 28, 1976 July-August (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Volumes 4:10, 6:6.
  - Guardian. Independent radical newsweekly, 1973 June 27 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Volume 25:37.
  - Guerilla, 1971 November 10 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Volume 2:22.
  - Highway 13, 1972? (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - However..., 1946 October (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Independent Socialist, 1976 March-Apr, September (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Volumes 2:6, 3.
  - Indian Voice, 1973 April (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Indications, 1971 May (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Individual Action, 1952 October 31 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Indochina (Journal of the Vietnam Solidarity Committee), 1969 September-1971 May, 1971 July-1972 May, 1972 October-November (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
    Volumes 1:1-1:11, 12-14, 16-20, 23. Volumes 1:1-1:7 titled Vietnam.
  - Indochina Bulletin, 1973 July (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Volume 27.
  - Journal du Comité d'Information de la Faculté de Médecine de Paris, 1968 May 21, 26, 31, June 10-29 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    Volumes [unnumbered], 9, 13, 16-21.
  - Korea Focus, 1974 April-May, 1975 March-April (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Volumes 2:4, 4:1.
  - Labor Today, 1974 January-Feb, 1976 January (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Volumes 13:1-13:2, 15:1.
  - Last Post, 1971 October (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Left Face, 1970 March (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Volume 1:6.
  - Lesbian Connection, 1977 April (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Volume 3:1.
  - Leviathan, 1970 Mar, May (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Volumes 1:9, 2:1.
  - Liaison, 1962 November 17-1963 June 15 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Volumes 1:1-1:16.
  - Libera, 1972 Winter (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Liberation, 1971 Oct, 1972 May, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Volumes 16:5, 17:2, 17:10.
  - Liberation News Service
    - 1967 September-October 22, November 10, November 16-December 18 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
      Volumes [3 unnumbered (1-3?)], 4, 11, 13-21.
    - 1967 December 20-1968 March 22, March 27-May 13, May 21-June 11, June 18-21 (Box 11, Folder 1-10)
      Numbers 22-57, 59-73, 75-81, 83-84.
    - 1968 June 25-December 4, November 23, December 12, 19, 28 (Box 12, Folder 1-7)
      Numbers 85-118, 121, 125, 127, 129.
    - 1968 December 28 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Number 180.
  - Livre Blanc de la Réforme, 1968 June 14 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Logos (Montreal), 1972 October 10 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - London Bulletin, 1967 August (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - LU: Links Um! (Germany), 1975 Feb, Jun, November (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Madison-Milwaukee Bugle American, 1970 Sep16-26, October 1-21, November 12-18, December 3-9 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Volumes 1:1, 1:3-1:5, 1:9, 1:11.
  - The Marble Index, 1971? (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Matchbox, 1976 Winter (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Midnight, 1970 November 9 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Volume 17:17.
  - The Militant, 1971 April 30 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Modern Times, 1970 May 1-15, September 15, 1971 June 1-14, September 1-4, December 1-31, 1972 February 1-15, 1973 December 1-15, 1974 September 15-30, November 1-15, 1975 February 15-28 (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
    Volumes 1:1-1:2, 1:9, 2:3, 2:9, 2:15-2:16, 2:19, 4:13, 5:7, 5:10, 5:17.
  - Morning Report, 1972 June-July (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Volume 2:6.
  - Mr. Nebo Flash, 1972 November 14-27 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Movement, 1968 August (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Volume 4:7.
  - Movin' Together, 1971 September 21, November 8 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - MRP Bulletin (Movimiento Revolucionario Peronista), 1972 March (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Volume 2:12.
  - Myths and Techno-Fantasies, 1972? (Box 13, Folder 19)
    One unnumbered issue.
  - National Action Bulletin, 1968 October 31 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement, 1972 Jan, December (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Volumes 1:3, 2:3.
  - New Improved Truth, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New Left Notes (SDS), 1969 October 21, December 10, 1970 April (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New Politics News, 1967 September 25, November 15 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Volumes 1:4-1:5.
  - New Solidarity, 1972 June 19-23, July 3-21 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Volumes 3:12, 3:14-15, 3:16.
  - New York Review of Sex and Politics, 1969 Nov? (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Volume 1:19.
  - News Notes, 1967 May-August (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Volumes 19:3-19:4.
  - News of Greece, 1971 January-February (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Volume 4:1.
  - Next Step, 1971 December 18 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Nola Express, 1971 September 24-October 7 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Volume 90.
  - Northern Neighbors, 1971 Feb, 1972 December, 1974 Jun, December, 1975 Mar, December (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Volumes 161, supplement, 198, 203, 206, 214.
  - NUC Newsletter (New University Conference), 1969 August 15, September 15, November 4, December 15, 1970 January 15, February 5, March 15-May 8, September 15-1971 April 20, May 15-July 4, September-October 31 (Box 14, Folder 13-15)
    Volumes 3:1, 3:3, 3:6, 3:8, 3:10, 3:12, 3:14-3:17, 4:1-4:13, 4:15-4:17, 5:1-5:3.
  - NUC-MLC Newlsletter (New University Conference/Modern Language Caucus), 1969 October (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Nueva Hora (Argentina), 1972? (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Organo Oficial de la Organizacion Marxista Revolucionaria (Chile), 1972 March-August (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Numbers 2-3.
  - Off Our Backs, 1970 March 19, December 31, 1972 Summer, September (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Volumes 1:3, 1:15, 1:24, 2:1.
  - Offul Times, 1972 July 4, October 27 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Old Mole, 1968 September 18-1969 August 28, September 13-October 23, November 7-December 4, 1970 January 28-April 30 (Box 15, Folder 4-19)
    Volumes 1:1-1:5, 6-20, 22-24, 26-27, 31-37, Strike Specials 4, 7-9.
  - Open Sights, 1972 May (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Other Scenes, 1967 Jan?-April, Jun, September, 1968 February-Dec, 1969 February, April-August 15, September 30-1970 May (Box 16, Folder 1-8)
    Volumes 1:1-1-4, 1:11, 2:1-2:7, 3:2, 3:4, 3:6, 3:8-3:11, 3:14-4:5, scattered unnumbered issues.
  - Pac-O-Lies, 1969 December 25 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Palmares Marxismo y Revolución (Chile), 1972 March-June (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Volume 1:2-3.
  - The Paper, 1967 Summer, November 7 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Volumes 2:27, 3:3.
  - The Partisan, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Patria Nueva; Boletin de Grito de Asencio (Uruguay), 1971 June-July (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Volumes 2:20-2:21.
  - The Patriot, 1971 March 21-July 21 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Volumes 1:1-1:2.
  - Peace and Freedom, 1974 Oct, 1976 April-May (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Volumes 23:7, 36:4.
  - Peace News, 1971 September 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Number 1835.
  - The Peacemaker, 1967 July 15-29, October 7, 1968 June 8, 29 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Volumes 20:10-20:11, 20:13, 21:6, 21:8.
  - The Pentagon Paper, 1974 July-Aug, September (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Volumes 2,4.
  - People and Taxes, 1973 November (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - People's New Service (Black Panther, New Haven Chapter), 1970 April 5 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Number 14.
  - People's Voice (Irish), 1970 April (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives, 1967 November-December (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Volume 11/12.
  - Philadelphia Free Press, 1969 November 17 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Volume 2:23.
  - Philippines Information Bulletin, 1973 June-September (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - The Phoenix, 1971 June 29 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Volume 3:26.
  - Plain Dealer, 1970 April 30 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Volume 1:12.
  - PLAN: Politica Latinoamericana Nueva (Chile), 1972 September 12 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Volume 7:81.
  - Politicks and Other Human Interests. New York, 1978 March 28 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Posición del Socialismo para Todo el Pueblo (Chile), 1972 September 4, 26 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Volumes 1:21, 1:24.
  - Proper Gander, 1970 April-May (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Number 1.
  - Puerto Rico Libre, 1976 April (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Volume 4:8.
  - Punji Stick, 1971 April 24 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    volume 1:1.
  - Quicksilver Times, 1970 June 23-July 5 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Volume 2:15.
  - Race Relations Reporter, 1971 November 1-December 15, 1972 January 3-February 7, May (Box 17, Folder 26)
    Volume 2:20-2:23, 3:1-3:3, 3:6.
  - The Radical Therapist, 1971 October (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - The Rag, 1967 March 27, June 5, October 30, December 18 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Volumes 1:20, 1:26, 2:3, 2:9.
  - Rage, 1972 May (Box 17, Folder 29)
    Volume 1:7.
  - Rags, 1971 June (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Ramparts, 1968 July 27, 1970 June (Box 17, Folder 31)
    Volumes 7:1, 8:12.
  - Rat
    - 1968 Aug, October 18-31, 1969 May 22-June 4 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - 1970 March 7-21 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - La Raza, 1971, 1972 Jun, 1974 February (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Volumes 1:5-1:7, 2:1.
  - The Realist, 1967 February (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Volume 73.
  - Recon, 1976 July (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Volume 4:5.
  - Red Balloon, 1972 Mar? (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Red Buffalo, 1971 Summer (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Red Mole, 1970 October 16-31 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Red Pages, 1971 May 1, 1973 Spring (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Volume 1:1, unnumbered.
  - Red Papers, 1972 Apr, Oct, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Volumes 1:2, 4-5.
  - Red Star (Sitarah-i Surkh), 1971 September (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Renaissance: Nouveau Bulletin d'Information des Étudiants de Sciences Po, 1961 June (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Volume 17.
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement, 1969 October (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Rights, 1969 Sep, 1975 April-May, 1976 January-March (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rising Up Angry, 1971 September 28, November 6 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Volumes 3:4, 3:6.
  - Road, 1971 May 31-June 21 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Rock, 1971 April 26-June 21 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    Volumes 2:19-2:23.
  - Rolling Stone, 1969 April 5-July 12, 1971 September 16 (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
    Volumes 30-37, 91.
  - The Scene, 1977 March 11-25 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Volume 63.
  - Screw
    - 1969 September 8, 1970 June 1-8, September 7-14, November 30 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
      Numbers 27, 65-66, 79-80, 91.
    - 1970 December 7-14, 1971 April 26-May 10, May 24 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
      Numbers 92-93, 112-114, 116.
  - The Seattle Group, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Number 58.
  - Shakedown, 1970 April 24 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Volume 2:2.
  - Shelterforce, 1976 June-Winter (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Volumes 2:1-2:3.
  - Shot Tower, 1971 Aug, 1972 February (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Volumes 1:2, 1:5.
  - Socialist Tribune, 1971 September-October (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Volume 3:8.
  - Solares Hill, 1971 February 15-March 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Soul Force, 1968 February 15, 1971 November-December (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Volumes 1:1, 5:6.
  - Source Catalog: Communications, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Spare Change II, 1972 August 16-30 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Spark, 1972 September 6-November 29, 1973 May 15-June 12, July 20-August 17, October 27-November 24 (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
    Volumes 2:1-2:4, 2:10, 2:12, 3:2.
  - Staff
    - 1971 November 26-December 2, 1972 January 21-February 24 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
      Volumes 1:12, 1:20-1:24.
    - 1972 February 25-March 30 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      Volumes 1:25-1:29.
  - Statehood Call: Voice of the DC Statehood Party, 1972 February (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Stripes and Stars, 1973 February-November (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Volumes 1:1-1:6.
  - Struggle (University Students' Union of Addis Ababa), 1969 November (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Volumes no number, 5:2.
  - Student (Netherlands), 1970 October-November (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Volume 7:2.
  - The Student Mobilizer, 1968 October (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Task Force, 1968 October 25 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Tempo, 1970 May 15 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Tesis Proletarias (Chile), 1972 July (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Tiên Phong (Avant Garde), 1971 February-March (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Volume 5.
  - Tin Drum, 1971 Summer-1972 Summer (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Volumes 3:2-4:2.
  - Toward Revolutionary Art, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Tri-Continental Information Bulletin, 1967 July-October (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Volumes 1:3-1:5.
  - Tricontinentale Sorbonne, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Two...Three...Many, 1971 Spring (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - UConn Free Press, 1970 March 19 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Volume 1:8.
  - Unidade e Luta (Brazil), 1972 July-August (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - United Irishman, 1972 October-November (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - University Review, 1970 Apr, 1971 Oct?, 1972 Dec, 1973 March (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Volumes 2:7, 19, 26-27.
  - Up Against the Wall, Undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Four unnumbered issues.
  - U.R.P.E. Newsletter (Union for Radical Political Economics), 1970 Fall (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Venceremos, 1973 July 1-15 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Volume 3:7.
  - Venceremos (Chile), 1972 July 15 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Volumes 2:21.